JARRED TAYLOR

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

DETAILS

ADDRESS

Remote United States

PHONE

314-398-3570

EMAIL

jarrede20@gmail.com

LINKS

Interactive Portfolio

GitHub Portfolio

LinkedIn

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

JavaScript

• • • • •

ReactJS

• • • • •

HTML & CSS

• • • •

Python

 \bullet \bullet \bullet \circ

Java

• • • 0 0

PHP

• • • 0 0

PROFILE

Currently serving in the United States Air Force, I am also working as a Freelance Web Developer while also pursuing a degree in Software Engineering. As a developer, I am comfortable with Python, JavaScript, ReactJS & HTML/CSS with an expanding comprehension of Java & PHP Specializing in web development, I am also growing my knowledge in machine learning & data analytics.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Freelance Web Developer

Mar 2020 — Present

I create web applications for various clients ranging from logistical companies, e-commerce platforms, tech startups, informative web pages, blogs, plus more. As a web developer, I specialize in JavaScript, ReactJS, HTML, & CSS.

United States Air Force

Nov 2019 — Present

Airborne Mission Systems Specialist - Responsible for operating the radar, communications, and electronic equipment. Contributing to the management of the battlespace during tactical and strategic missions by coordinating all of the necessary data received on airborne command centers.

EDUCATION

BS, Software Engineering, Arizona State University

Online - ABET Accreditated

May 2021 — Present

Expected to graduate in December of 2023

BBA, International Business, Minnesota State University Moorhead

Moorhead, MN

Aug 2018 — May 2019

Departed this university to join the United States Air Force.

CERTIFICATIONS

React Development Certification, Programming Hub

Mar 2021 — Mar 2021

HTML & CSS Certification, Programming Hub

Oct 2020 — Oct 2020

Complete Web Development Bootcamp, Udemy

Nov 2020 — Jan 2021